HERE Editor Files 6199/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Editor Files
1973-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/015
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
6766113
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 22, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), was a labor union for workers in the hospitality industry and was formed in 1891. HERE merged with the Union of Neddletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE), in 2004, to form UNITE HERE. HERE and later UNITE HERE were affiliated with the AFL-CIO until September of 2005, when the General Executive Board of UNITE HERE voted to leave the AFL-CIO and join in with the Change to Win Coalition.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199 AV: HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 G: HERE Graphics 6199 MB: HERE Memorabilia 6199 mf: HERE Records on Microfilm 6199 PUBS: HERE Publications 6199/001: HERE Legislative Department Files 6199/002: HERE Western Region Local Files 6199/003: HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files 6199/003 mf: HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/004: HERE Locals files 6199/004 mf: HERE Locals Files on Microfilm 6199/005: HERE Communications Department Files 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/006: HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006 mf: HERE General Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf: HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/008 mf: HERE General President's Files on Microfilm 6199/009 mf: HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf: HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/011 mf: HERE Official Journals on Microfilm 6199/012 mf: HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/013: HERE Historical Files 6199/013 P: HERE Historical Photographs 6199/014: HERE Conventions Files
Textile industry -- New York (State); Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing trade -- New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6766113
- Black History Month, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Board Meeting, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Canadian Labor Council. CLC, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Catering Industry Employee. Costs, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Catering Industry Employee. Upgrades., 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Convention. 39th., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Convention. 41st., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Frontier Sold., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Gibson, John. Indictment Press Releases., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- HERE History., 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Index Project. Editorial Experts. [5.25" floppies], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Irish Transport and General Workers' Union, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- IRS, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Japan Air Lines and Nikko Hotels. JAL / Nikko, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Labor History., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Labor Press Contacts. (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Labor Studies., 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Latinos., 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- New Leadership. (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Marriot Inns., 1973-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Miami. $5 Million Payback., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Miami. Strike., 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Yale Strike. Folder 1, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Yale Strike. Folder 2, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)